I've been feeling very heavy.
And then this morning, right before I woke up,
because this is when I get my downloads,
my ancestors said, you were built for this time.
You were sent for this time.
And it brought me so much peace
because it just gave me a centering of confidence
and also of calm
that everything that's happening right now
is terrible and horrible,
and I'm supposed to be here for it.
And if I'm supposed to be here for it,
then I am equipped to do something about it.
And the part that breaks me is always the feeling
that I'm doing nothing and that I can't do anything about it.
And this download came to me and said,
no, you were sent for this time.
So you're doing, continue to do,
and this weight that's on you
is what you were made to carry.
So don't think about the weight.
Keep moving towards where you're going.
And where I feel we're going
is I feel we're breaking on through to the other side.
I do.
I refuse to believe that these devils
have an inevitable win.
We're in a war of the worlds,
which reminded me that I need to rewatch
War of the Worlds.
But if you watch the movie War of the Worlds,
I mean, that's what they're doing to us
is what the aliens do in War of the Worlds.
And we know that these movies
are essentially them telling us the truth.
Again, you know,
whether or not these people are aliens
is still left to be determined.
However, what they are,
regardless of if they're extraterrestrial or not,
are folks who are mining us of our energy
for their own desires of demise.
So let that carry you.
I hope it can,
because it's carrying me.
We were sent here for this time
to be a light in the darkness.
to guide us to the other side.
You know I'm going to make a song about it.
Support a real one.